Indian Neck Folk Festival collection, 1961-2015
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series II: Sound Recordings, 1961-2014
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival, May 2010, 1 sound cassette (DAT): digital. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR396)
    DAT 2 of 2. Saturday evening concert with the Sugar River Band and the Orzechowskis, Half Johnson (Bonnie Miller, Joy Bennett), Jerry Epstein, Dan Milner, Allison Kiphuth, Brian Cartwright and Suzanne Mrozak, Dave Howard and Frank Stettner, Chris Koldewey, Kathy Westra, Edmund and Charmion Thomas, Lisa Null, Ben Borscht and the Beats, Pamela Goddard, Joyful Noise, Michael Gibney, Maggie Bye, David Gibney, the Scholarship Kids, Alicia Best, John Roberts, and Robbie Wedeen.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival, May 2011, 1 sound cassette (DAT): digital. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR397)
    DAT 1 of 3. Saturday evening concert with George Balderose, Willie Donaldson, Autumn Rose Lester, Glyn Collinson, Kim Wallach, Ariel Temple, Old New England, Audi Lane, Deirdre Murhta, Ryan and Brennish Thompson, Sarah Berlin and the Sonic Hedgehogs, Robbie Wedeen, Drew Smith, Mike Resnick, Rick Lee, Caroline and David Paton, Shannon Paton, Joanie Bronfman, Neal MacMillan, Maggie Bye, Mark Maniak and the Moral Supporters, Bonner McAllester, Tom Hodgson, Anna Nowogrodzki and Ian McGullam, Sue West, and others.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival, May 2011, 1 sound cassette (DAT): digital. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR398)
    DAT 2 of 3. Saturday evening concert with Joyful Noise, Mark Gilston, Kathy Westra, George Stevens, Tom Hodgson, Tim Woodbridge, Dave Howard, David Jones, Ken Sweeney, Ben Borscht and the Beats, Frank Stettner, Anything Goes (Ben Koenig and Mark Greenberg), Brian Cartwright and Suzanne Mrozak, Lisa Null, Jerry Epstein, George Balderose and Bennett Hammond, John Roberts, Pamela Goddard, Phil Zimmerman, Dick Levine, Lorraine and Bennett Hammond, and others.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival, May 2011, 1 sound cassette (DAT): digital. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR399)
    DAT 3 of 3. Saturday evening concert with Annie Wickersty, Bob Clayton, Elizabeth and Sandy LaPrelle, Jonathan Leiss, Murray Callahan, Rose Sheehan and Colin de la Barre, Elizabeth Burke, John Burke, and Andy May, Charlie Baum, Heather Wood, Frank Stettner, and others.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival, May 11, 2012, 1 sound cassette (DAT): digital. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR400)
    DAT 1 of 3. Saturday evening concert with George Balderose, Caroline Paton, Shingle the Roof (Kate Spencer, Tim Woodbridge, Jerry Devokaitis), Ryan and Brennish Thompson, Judy Cook, Harvey Tolman, Jeri Corlew and Kathy Westra and George Stephens, Dave Howard and Frank Stettner, Ben Borscht and the Beats, Deanna Stiles and Bob McQuillen, Dave Kiphuth, Ann Schunior and Neal MacMillan, Bob Clayton, Planet Banjo, Martha Burns, Autumn Rose Lester, Chris Koldewey, Julia Friend, Ian McGullam and Anna Nowogrodzki, Ken Sweeney, Bob Stuart, Mahati Chintapalli, and others.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival, May 11, 2012, 1 sound cassette (DAT): digital. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR401)
    DAT 2 of 3. Saturday evening concert with George Balderose, Caroline Paton, Shingle the Roof (Kate Spencer, Tim Woodbridge, Jerry Devokaitis), Ryan and Brennish Thompson, Judy Cook, Harvey Tolman, Jeri Corlew and Kathy Westra and George Stephens, Dave Howard and Frank Stettner, Ben Borscht and the Beats, Deanna Stiles and Bob McQuillen, Dave Kiphuth, Ann Schunior and Neal MacMIllan, Bob Clayton, Planet Banjo, Martha Burns, Autumn Rose Lester, Chris Koldewey, Julia Friend, Ian McGullam and Anna Nowogrodzki, Ken Sweeney, Bob Stuart, Mahati Chintapalli, and others.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival, May 11, 2012, 1 sound cassette (DAT): digital. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR402)
    DAT 3 of 3. Saturday evening concert with George Balderose, Caroline Paton, Shingle the Roof (Kate Spencer, Tim Woodbridge, Jerry Devokaitis), Ryan and Brennish Thompson, Judy Cook, Harvey Tolman, Jeri Corlew and Kathy Westra and George Stephens, Dave Howard and Frank Stettner, Ben Borscht and the Beats, Deanna Stiles and Bob McQuillen, Dave Kiphuth, Ann Schunior and Neal MacMillan, Bob Clayton, Planet Banjo, Martha Burns, Autumn Rose Lester, Chris Koldewey, Julia Friend, Ian McGullam and Anna Nowogrodzki, Ken Sweeney, Bob Stuart, Mahati Chintapalli, and others.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival, May 11, 2013, 1 sound cassette (DAT): digital. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR403)
    DAT 1 of 2. Saturday evening concert with Kathy Westra, Jane's Gang (Jane Rothfield, Amy Buckingham, Bob Buckingham), Linda Prager, Dick Levine, Caroline Paton, Shingle the Roof (Jerry Devokaitis, Kate Spencer, Tim Woodbridge), Bob Stuart, Phil Zimmerman, Joanie Bronfman, Neal MacMillan, Ann Schunior), Danny Spooner, Claire Boucher, Brad Hurley, Ariel Temple, Kim Wallach, Free Range Orphans (Riki Schneyer, Milan Pavich, John Wenstrom, Jessica Wenstrom, Robin Murie), Pamela Goddard, Ken Sweeney, Jimmy, Cisco, and Me, Bruce Foley and Mary Coogan, Larry Hanks and Deborah Robins, the Bridge (Linda Prager, Sarah Pilzer, Judy Meiselman, Robbie Wedeen, Nicole Singer), David Weisberg, Joy Bennett and Chris Koldewey, Carol Hausner, Rachel Sucher, and Mark Greenberg, Murray Callahan, John Roberts, Claire Boucher, Brian Cartwright, Ben Borscht and the Beats, Lorraine and Bennett Hammond, and others.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival, May 11, 2013, 1 sound cassette (DAT): digital. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR404)
    DAT 2 of 2. Saturday evening concert with Ryan and Brennish Thompson, Martha Burns, INFF Shape Note Singers, David Jones, Bonnie Milner, Kathy Westra, Dave Howard, Robin Murie, John Wenstrom, Jessica Wenstrom, Riki Schneyer, Milan Pavich, Shona and Allan Carr, Anything Goes (Mark Greenberg), Jane Rothfield, Allan Carr, and Tom Hodgson, Max Godfrey, Heather Wood, Robbie Wedeen, Drew Smith, and Mike Resnick, Rose Sheehan and Colin de la Barre, DNA (George Balderose, Jacob Henderson, Bennett Hammond, Steve Carrigan, Ruthie Byers, Lonesome Dave and the Usual Suspects (Dave Kiphuth, Phil Zimmerman, Frank Stettner), Meridian (Colin de la Barre and Olivia Gale), Chris Carpenter, the Usual Suspects (Phil Zimmerman, Frank Stettner, Larry Marschall, Neil Rossi, Mark Greenberg), and others.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival, May 9, 2014, 1 sound cassette (DAT): digital. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR405)
    DAT 1 of 2. Saturday evening concert with Jennifer Woods, Ben Borscht and the Beats, Fran and Lisa Mandeville, Neil Rossi, Dave Kiphuth, David Weisberg and Adam Shapiro, Penny Anderson and Linda Prager, the Fiddling Thompsons (Ryan and Brennish) and Susie Dean Miller, Dick Levin, Ken Sweeney, Caroline Paton, Kate Seeger and Dean Spencer, Julie's Original Tune Set (Julie Sorcek, Susie Dean, Susan Burke), Rose Sheehan, John Roberts, Lorraine and Bennett Hammond, Phil Zimmerman, George Stephens and Kathy Westra, Neal MacMillan and Joanie Bronfman, Elizabeth Burke and Susannah Branch, Kossoy Sisters (Irene Saletan and Ellen Christenson), Mark Gilston, Pamela Goddard, Pete Kraemer and Bob Clayton, Riki Schneyer and the Free Range Orphans, Brian Dolphin, Jerry Devokaitis, Martha Burns, Dave Howard, and others.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival, May 9, 2014, 1 sound cassette (DAT): digital. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR406)
    DAT 2 of 2. Saturday evening concert with Heather Wood and Ken Schatz, Max Godfrey, Elijah Wald and Sandrine Shown, Peter and Audio Souza, Final Tune in Remembrance of Bob McQuillen (Susie Dean Miller, Ryan and Brenish Thompson, Art Bryan, Julie Sorcek, Neal MacMillan, Richard and Lizze Backes), and others.
- Series III: Graphic Materials, 1961-2007
  Black-and-white and color photographic prints and negatives from the Indian Neck Folk Festival. Includes approximately 33 8x10 in., 112 5x7 in., 385 4x6 in., and 121 3x5 in. and smaller photographic prints. Also includes 54 film negatives. There are an additional 4453 digital still image files (JPEG) in Series V: Optical Media.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival, 1961, 1969 (Box-folder 4/1)
    Black-and-white photographic print by Joe Alper. Indian Neck Folk Festival, 1961, Montowese House, Indian Neck Point, Branford, Connecticut.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival photographs, mostly by Alan B. Schwartz, 1969 (Box-folder 4/2)
    Black-and-white photographic prints mostly taken by Alan B. Schwartz. Includes photographs of musicians and performers, such as Gordon Bok, Tom Paley, Artie Rose, and Roy Berkeley. Backsides of photographs are labelled with performer names.
  - Gordon Bok in concert, May 1969 (Box-folder 4/3)
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival, May 1975 (Box-folder 4/4)
    Black-and-white photographic prints mostly taken by Jay Smith. Includes photographs of musicians and performers, such as Roy Berkeley, Cliff Haslam, Jonathan Eberhart, Reed Martin, and Maggi Peirce. Backsides of photographs are labelled with performer names.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival, May 1976 (Box-folder 4/5)
    Black-and-white photographic prints mostly taken by Jay Smith. Includes photographs of musicians and performers, such as Archie Fisher, Hank Sapoznik, and Bob Carlin. Backsides of photographs are labelled with performer names.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival, 1978 (Box-folder 4/6)
    Black-and-white photographic prints, negatives, contact sheet, mostly taken by Ken Feit. Includes photographs of musicians and performers, such as Pete Colby, Neil Rossi, and Helen Schneyer. Backsides of photographs are labelled with performer names.
  - Folk musician photographs and promotional materials, ca. 1978-1985 (Box-folder 6/4)
    Color and black-and-white photographic prints, promotional materials, articles, and biographies of folk musicians such as Sandy and Caroline Paton and Gordon Bok.
  - Folk musician photographs and promotional materials, ca. 1978-1988 (Box-folder 6/5)
    Color and black-and-white photographic prints and promotional materials for folk musicians such as Cliff Haslam, Joe and Antoinette McKenna, Rick and Lorraine Lee, Nowell Sing We Clear, the Tony Trischka Band, Bob Franke, Battlefield Band, and the Soldier's Fancy.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival, 1980-1982 (Box-folder 4/7)
    Black-and-white and color photographs of musicians, such as Joe Hickerson, April Limber, Bob McQuillen, and Pete Colby. Backsides of photographs are labelled with performer names.
  - HACC concert series, Pennsylvania Folk Festival, 1982 (Box-folder 6/6)
    Photographic prints of the Harrisburg Area Community College (HACC) concert series. Tony Trischka and band, January 23, 1982; Paton Family children's concert, February 20, 1982. Also includes photographs from the Pennsylvania Folk Festival, Wilson College, 1982.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival, May 1988 (Box-folder 4/8)
    From original folder: "May be Robin Sprung? Really unknown." Includes color photographs of musicians, such as Cliff Haslam, April Limber, Bob McQuillen, and Pete Colby. Backsides of photographs are labelled with performer names.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival, May 1989 (Box-folder 4/9)
    Includes color photographs of musicians, such as Helen Schneyer, Peter and Mary Alice Amidon, and Maggi Peirce. Backsides of photographs are labelled with performer names.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival, May 1990 (Box-folder 4/10)
    Photographic prints mostly taken by Joan Sprung. Includes photographs of musicians and performers, such as Helen Schneyer, Bob Clayton, and Maggi Peirce. Backsides of photographs are labelled with performer names.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival, May 1991 (Box-folder 4/11)
    From original folder: "Jay's 25th year as director. Photographer unknown." Includes color photographs camp attendees, musicians and performers, such as Helen Schneyer, Joan Sprung, and Kathy Westra. Backsides of photographs are labelled with performer names.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival, May 1992 (Box-folder 4/12)
    Photographic prints from the 1992 Indian Neck Folk Festival. Backsides of photographs are labelled with performer names.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival, May 1993 (Box-folder 4/13)
    Color photographic prints from the 1992 Indian Neck Folk Festival. From original folder: "Joan Sprung and others. Ballad Charade - Tamlin." Backsides of photographs are labelled with performer names.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival, May 1994 (Box-folder 4/14)
    Color photographic prints and negatives from the 1994 Indian Neck Folk Festival. Backsides of photographs are labelled with performer names.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival, May 1996 (Box-folder 5/1)
    From original envelope: "Ralph Lee Smith sandal shop reunion, [Joan] Sprung. Ralph asked us to invite the people who hung out at Allan Block's sandal shop in NYC before he moved to NH." Color photographic prints from the 1996 Indian Neck Folk Festival. Backsides of photographs are labelled with performer names.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival, May 1998 (Box-folder 5/2)
    Color photographic prints from the 1998 Indian Neck Folk Festival, taken by Charlie West. Photographs of Ballad Charade, Lord Bateman. Cast members' names written on to original folder.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival, May 1999 (Box-folder 5/3)
    Color photographic prints from the 1999 Indian Neck Folk Festival, taken by Charlie West. Backsides of photographs are labelled with performer names.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival, May 2000 (Box-folder 5/4)
    Color photographic prints from the 2000 Indian Neck Folk Festival. From original sleeve of photographs: "Will you bob your hair girls; Play; Ballad charade." Backsides of photographs are labelled with performer names.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival, Roy Berkeley, May 2001 (Box-folder 5/5)
    Color photographic prints from the 2001 Indian Neck Folk Festival, taken by Roy Berkeley. Backsides of photographs are labelled with performer names.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival, Newcomb/McCade, May 2001 (Box-folder 5/6)
    Color photographic prints from the 2001 Indian Neck Folk Festival, taken by Newcomb/McCade and others. From original sleeve of photographs: "After breakfast on Sunday people stay in the dining hall to sing 'God songs.' These pictures are all from that session in 2001." Backsides of photographs are labelled with performer names.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival, Roy Berkeley, May 2002 (Box-folder 5/7-8)
    Color photographic prints from the 2002 Indian Neck Folk Festival, taken by Roy Berkeley. Backsides of photographs are labelled with performer names.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival, Charles West, May 2002 (Box-folder 6/1)
    Color photographic prints from the 2002 Indian Neck Folk Festival, taken by Charles West. Includes photographs from the ballad charade.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival, Roy Berkeley, May 2003 (Box-folder 6/2)
    Color photographic prints from the 2003 Indian Neck Folk Festival, taken by Roy Berkeley. Backsides of photographs are labelled with performer names.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival, 2006-2007 (Box-folder 6/3)
    Color photographic prints from the 2006 and 2007 Indian Neck Folk Festivals.
- Series IV: Moving Images, 1988-1997
  VHS tapes of performances from Indian Neck Folk Festivals. Tapes have been digitized and are accessible in the Folklife Reading Room. There are an additional 152 digital video files (MOV and MP4) in Series V: Optical Media.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival, 1988, 1 videocassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: MV001)
    Festival recording. Kate Spencer, videographer.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival, 1994, 1 videocassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: MV002)
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival performances, 1997, 1 videocassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: MV003)
    Three performances. Lisa Neustadt et. al., Yorkist Ballad Charade, and Joan Sprung and Sara Grey.
- Series V: Optical Media, ca. 1965-2015
  CD-Rs, DVD-Rs, and thumb drives containing audio, video, and still image digital files from the Indian Neck Folk Festival. The following material is unprocessed, and descriptions are transcribed from the original media.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival, 1965, 1 CD-R: digital. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: CF042)
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival, 1965, 1 CD-R: digital. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: CF043)
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival, 1965, 1 CD-R: digital. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: CF044)
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival, 1966, 1 CD-R: digital. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: CF041)
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival, 1969, 1 CD-R: digital. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: CF039)
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival, 1969, 1 CD-R: digital. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: CF040)
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival, 2000, 1 CD-R: digital. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: CF002)
    Singing in dining room.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival, May 2000, 1 CD-R: digital. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: CF046)
    Part 1. Saturday night concert.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival, May 2000, 1 CD-R: digital. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: CF047)
    Part 2. Saturday night concert.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival, May 2000, 1 CD-R: digital. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: CF048)
    Part 3. Saturday night concert.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival, 2000-05, 1 CD-R: digital. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: CF049)
    Part 4. Saturday night concert.
  - Unidentified content, ca. 2000-2014, 1 Thumb drive: digital. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: CF034)
    Indian Neck concert videos from Marcia Goodman.
  - Unidentified content, ca. 2000-2014, 1 Thumb drive: digital. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: CF035)
  - Photographs from Indian Neck Folk Festival, 2001, 2002, 1 CD-R: digital. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: CF020)
    Susan Sterngold.
  - Photographs from Indian Neck Folk Festival, 2002, 2007, 1 CD-R: digital. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: CF019)
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival, 2003, 2013, 1 CD-R: digital. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: CF021)
    "Probably Jim McDade, photographer."
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival, 2004, 1 CD-R: digital. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: CF032)
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival, 2004, 1 CD-R: digital. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: CF022)
    "Various years from Jim McDade."
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival, 2005, 1 CD-R: digital. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: CF023)
    Photographs by Jim McDade.
  - Photographs from Indian Neck Folk Festival, May 2005, 1 CD-R: digital. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: CF018)
    Charlie West.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival, 2006, 1 CD-R: digital. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: CF033)
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival, 2006, 1 CD-R: digital. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: CF036)
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival, 2006, 1 CD-R: digital. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: CF037)
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival, 2006, 1 CD-R: digital. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: CF038)
  - Photographs from Indian Neck Folk Festival, 2006, 1 DVD-R: digital. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: CF011)
    "2006 INFF Pictures, Charlie West, Fred Von Graf."
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival, 2007, 1 CD-R: digital. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: CF045)
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival, 2007, 2008, 1 CD-R: digital. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: CF027)
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival, May 12, 2007, 1 CD-R: digital. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: CF016)
    Camper Concert.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival, May 12, 2007, 1 CD-R: digital. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: CF017)
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival, 2008, 1 CD-R: digital. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: CF003)
    2008 concert.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival, 2009, 1 CD-R: digital. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: CF028)
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival, 2009, 1 CD-R: digital. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: CF029)
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival, 2009, 1 CD-R: digital. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: CF030)
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival, 2009, 1 CD-R: digital. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: CF031)
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival, 2009, 1 CD-R: digital. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: CF024)
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival, 2009, 1 CD-R: digital. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: CF004)
    Audio from festival.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival, January 3, 2009, 1 CD-R: digital. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: CF005)
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival, February 3, 2009, 1 CD-R: digital. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: CF006)
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival, March 3, 2009, 1 CD-R: digital. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: CF007)
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival, 2011, 1 CD-R: digital. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: CF013)
    "Photos by Barb Trow."
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival, 2011, 1 CD-R: digital. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: CF025)
  - Photographs from Indian Neck Folk Festival, 2012, 1 CD-R: digital. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: CF014)
    "Photos 2012 INFF Concert by Marcia Goodman."
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival, 2012, 1 CD-R: digital. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: CF026)
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival, 2012, 1 CD-R: digital. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: CF008)
    2012 concert.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival, 2015, 1 DVD-R: digital. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: CF001)
    Saturday concert, beginning. Courtesy Sarah Newcomb, videographer.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival, 2015, 1 CD-R: digital. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: CF009)
    Saturday concert.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival Concert Playlists, January 16, 2016, 1 CD-R: digital. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: CF010)
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival, undated, 1 CD-R: digital. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: CF015)
    "End Indian Neck."
  - Photographs, undated, 1 DVD-R: digital. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: CF012)
    "INFF Photos from Skit Dhu."
- Series VI: Oversize Materials, ca. 1981-1990
  - Posters and printing plates for concerts, ca. 1981-1990, 8 posters; 6 metal plates, various sizes (Box-folder 7/1)
    Posters and printing plates for concerts that Indian Neck Folk Festival and the Pennsylvania Folk Festival presented, including those with Gordon Bok, Lorraine Lee, the Charles River Valley Boys, Mike Seeger, Utah Phillips, and Bill Staines.
- Appendix A: Concert Playlists